renewbuy.com 2019-05-23

# Privacy Policy | RenewBuy

  * Privacy Policy

**WE RESPECT YOUR PRIVACY! PERIOD!** And we will never do anything to invade it.

As real people on the other side of this website we understand how irritating persistant phone calls can be. So we promise to keep it down to the bare minimum and prefer to remind you through emails that too without spamming your inbox.

**Here is how our legal team has worded the document. If you want go through it but it  will probably put you to sleep**.

By using the website and/or registering yourself at RenewBuy.com you authorize M/S D2C Insurance Broking Pvt Ltd, our other affiliates & associated partners to contact you via email or phone call or SMS and offer you their services for the product you have opted for basis your needs, imparting product knowledge, offering insurance solutions, offer other promotional offers running on website for which reasons personally identifiable information may be collected as detailed below. And irrespective of the fact if also you have registered yourself under DND or DNC or NCPR service, you still authorize us to give you a call from the RenewBuy, M/S D2C Insurance Broking Pvt Ltd & associated partners for the above-mentioned purposes till 45 days of your registration with us.

This Privacy Policy covers M/S D2C Insurance Broking Pvt Ltd’s treatment of personally identifiable information that M/S D2C Insurance Broking Pvt Ltd’s collects when you are on the RenewBuy site and you use its services. This policy also covers M/S D2C Insurance Broking Pvt Ltd’s treatment of any personally identifiable information that it business partners share with it. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that M/S D2C Insurance Broking Pvt Ltd does not own or control or to people that it does not employ or manage.

M/S D2C Insurance Broking Pvt Ltd collects personally identifiable information when you register for the RenewBuy account, when you use certain M/S D2C Insurance Broking Pvt Ltd’s products or services, when you visit the various RenewBuy pages, and when you enter promotions or sweepstakes. M/S D2C Insurance Broking Pvt Ltd may also receive personally identifiable information from our business partners.

Also during registration, you may be requested to register your mobile phone and email id, pager, or other device to receive text messages, notifications, and other services to your wireless device. By registration you authorize us to send sms/email alerts to you for your login details and any other service requirements or some advertising messages/emails from us.

"We use cookies and other technologies such as pixel tags and clear gifs to store certain types of information each time you visit any page on our website. Cookies enable this website to recognize the information you have consented to give to this website and help us determine what portions of this website are most appropriate for your professional needs. We may also use cookies to serve advertising banners to you. These banners may be served by us or by a third party on our behalf. These cookies will not contain any personal information."

"Whether you want your web browser to accept cookies or not is up to you. If you haven't changed your computer's settings, most likely your browser already accepts cookies. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience all features of the website. You can also delete your browser cookies of disable them entirely. But this may significantly impact your experience with our website and may make parts of our website non functional or inaccessible. We recommend that you leave them turned on."

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

M/S D2C Insurance Broking Pvt Ltd will not sell or rent your personally identifiable information to anyone other than as specifically noted herein. Notwithstanding the foregoing, M/S D2C Insurance Broking Pvt Ltd may share, sell and/or transfer your personally identifiable information to an affiliate and/or associate partner. M/S D2C Insurance Broking Pvt Ltd may also share, sell, and/or transfer your personally identifiable information to any successor-in-interest as a result of a sale of any part of M/S D2C Insurance Broking Pvt Ltd business or upon the merger, reorganization or consolidation of M/S D2C Insurance Broking Pvt Ltd with another entity on a basis that M/S D2C Insurance Broking Pvt Ltd is not the surviving entity. For the purposes of this paragraph, "affiliate" means any person directly, or indirectly through one or more intermediaries, that controls, is controlled by or is under common control with M/S D2C Insurance Broking Pvt Ltd. The term "control," as used in the immediately preceding sentence, shall mean with respect to any person, the possession, directly or indirectly, of the power, through the exercise of voting rights, contractual rights or otherwise, to direct or cause the direction of the management or policies of the controlled person. As used in this Privacy Policy, the term "person" includes any natural person, corporation, partnership, Limited Liability Company, trust, unincorporated association or any other entity.

"If you are no longer interested in receiving e-mail announcements and other marketing information from us, or you want us to remove any PII that we have collected about you, please e-mail your request to support@renewbuy.com."

How we protect your information We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

Sensitive and private data exchange between the Site and its Users happens over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protected with digital signatures

**Legal**

We strictly follow the norms of non disclosure agreement. It is our endeavor to ensure that the websites linked to us are safe and secure. However we have no control over 3rd party websites. Given our legal responsibilities to legal authorities and regulators, there may be situations when we need to share your information with legal authorities or processes or need to protect our right or comply by terms and conditions and the law of the land.

**Other sites**

There might be affiliates or other sites linked to our web site. Personal information thatyou provide to those sites are not our property. The affiliated sites may have different privacy practices and we encourage you to read their privacy policies. These sites may place their cookies or other files on your computer, collect data or solicit personal information.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

M/S D2C Insurance Broking Pvt Ltd may amend this policy from time to time, at our discretion. If we make any substantial changes in the way we use your personal information we will notify you by posting the changes here on these Privacy Policy pages.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this website, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Associated Partners**

General Insurance - Apollo Munich Health Insurance Company Limited, Bajaj Allianz General Insurance Co. Ltd., Bharti AXA General Insurance Company Limited, Cholamandalam MS General Insurance Co. Ltd., Future Generali India Insurance Company Limited, HDFC ERGO General Insurance Co. Ltd., ICICI Lombard General Insurance Co. Ltd., IFFCO Tokio General Insurance Co. Ltd., L&T General Insurance Company Limited, Max Bupa Health Insurance Company Ltd., National Insurance Co. Ltd., Raheja QBE General Insurance Company Limited, Reliance General Insurance Co. Ltd., Royal Sundaram Alliance Insurance Co. Ltd., SBI General Insurance Company Limited, Shriram General Insurance Company Limited., Star Health and Allied Insurance Company Limited, Tata AIG General Insurance Co. Ltd., The New India Assurance Co. Ltd., The Oriental Insurance Co. Ltd., United India Insurance Co. Ltd., Universal Sompo General Insurance Co. Ltd. 

Not-withstanding anything mentioned before, we reserve the right to contact you via any mechanisms, not limited to email, sms, or phone calls, to solicit feedback of your experience and to provide any additional services that you would be eligible for, either as a customer or as a visitor. We should not be held liable for any damages occurring to you as part of feedback solicitation and additional service provision.
